

PROFILE

A business oriented, proactive and problem-solving corporate counsel with in house experience in Banking and Finance Industry.

An ardent communicator with ability to relate people across all hierarchical level in the organization.

Proficient in building positive and productive working relationship and ability to communicate effectively with both stakeholders and colleagues with good interpersonal skills, good time management and prioritization proficiency.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+91 9673501727

ADDRESS:

B21, Nilgiri heights, Shivaji Housing Society, Senapati Bapat Road, 411016.

Mobile no: 9673501727

EMAIL:

niyati.morajkar@gmail.com

PERSONAL DETAILS

DATE OF BIRTH 1 May 1990

NIYATI GOVENKAR

LEGAL PROFFESSIONAL WITH MORE THAN 7 YEARS EXPERIENCE

EDUCATION

LL.M:(Corporate Laws) - 2014 Symbiosis Law School, Pune

LL.B - 2012

V.M. Salgaokar College of Law, Goa University

WORK EXPERIENCE

Poonawalla Fincorp Limited - Chief Manager - Corporate Legal From July 2021 to Present

PNB Housing Finance Limited - Regional legal Manager From December 2017 to July 2021

Kotak Mahindra Bank Limited - Deputy Legal Manager From September 2014 to December 2017

KEY DELIVERABLES

- Drafting, negotiating and review of Master Service Agreements, Non-Disclosure Agreements, Letter of Engagements, Leave & License Agreements, Master Lease Agreements, HR related letters, Memorandum of Understanding, Affidavits, Power of Attorney, Indemnity Bonds, Recovery Notices, etc.
- Assisted in filing trademark applications.
- Review and Negotiations of Treasury related transactions with different financial institutions.
- Working for Home Loan, Loan against Property, Working Capital Loan, Rural Housing Finance Vertical.
- Vetting Title search reports, Valuation reports, Creation of mortgage documents and general legal compliance documents.
- Handling other miscellaneous functions such as engaging in Negotiations & Liaison with the parties, police officials and various government officials in relation of matters related to company dedicatedly & promptly.
- Preparing & sending statutory notices to the defaulting borrowers

LANGUAGE KNOWN:

English, Hindi, Konkani & Marathi

Marital Status:

Married

HOBBIES

Travel Reading

CHERISHED VALUES

Insightful Sincere Patient

REFERENCE

Available on request

- Co-ordination with the Property searchers and ROC searchers and taking the Reports Monitoring the Sanction Terms and conditions of the financial facilities provided by the bank.
- Negotiations with parties for the recovery of outstanding dues of the defaulting borrowers.
- Vetting of all sorts of escrow agreements.
- Legal checking of all security documents as per loan agreement.
- Complying all provisions relating with Stamp Act and Registration Act.
- Advocate and agency interaction.
- Support CERSAI related follow up.
- ROC search, Charge creation and its follow up.
- Preparing MIS

COMPUTER SKILLS

MS Office

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Drafting, Negotiations, Review, Research, Strong Administration and Management Skills, Knowledge of Mortgage & Property Laws, Excellent Communication, Strong Leadership, Capable to Explore and Learn, Time Management.